{
    "subject": "resource/David_Parks_(politician)",
    "predicate": "property/branch",
    "object": "resource/United_States_Air_Force",
    "human_readable": "David Parks (politician) serves in the United States Air Force.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9240130186080933,
            "question": "What role does David Parks hold in the US Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080749750137329,
            "question": "Is David Parks a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8374111652374268,
            "question": "What branch of the US military does David Parks serve in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7819263935089111,
            "question": "Is David Parks involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7592445611953735,
            "question": "Where does David Parks serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5966817736625671,
            "question": "What is David Parks' profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799745321273804,
            "question": "What is David Parks' current role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5491152405738831,
            "question": "Does David Parks have a military background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5367140769958496,
            "question": "What type of government position does David Parks hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3881359398365021,
            "question": "David Parks is known for his work in what field?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Parks (politician) serves in the United States Air Force.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5453_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of government position does David Parks hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5453_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does David Parks have a military background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5453_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is David Parks' current role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5453_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5453_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5453/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt mentions that David Parks served four years in the U.S. Air Force, closeted, at Nellis."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that David Parks served in the U.S. Air Force between 1967 and 1971, which supports the statement that he served in the United States Air Force."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}